MATEUSZ NIEDBAŁ

Junior Java Developer

& + 48 515 344 571

Wroclaw, Poland (ready to relocate)

https://mrndesign.herokuapp.com

Skills

Programming Junior Skills:

JAVA 8 and above , Android, Spring, Hibernate, MySQL, SQLite, HTML5, ThymeLeaf, REST, GWT, Mongo DB, CSS, Maven, Git, Gradle

Programming tools: Intellij, Android Studio, Rabbit, Postman, Unix shell;

Programming Basics: C++, C#, PHP, Wordpress, Javascript;

Graphics: 3D MAX, Photoshop;

OS I work on: Windows, Linux;

Soft skills:

ability to work under the time pressure, involvement, creative problem solving, team work, quick knowledge taker;



report is available

Foreign languages

- English B2/C1
- ➤ German A1/A2

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).

About me

I am **ambitious** and **highly motivated** to start a career in IT field prepared for internship and/or remote/ full time work. My goal is to be a **valuable team member** in a **long** - **term collaboration** that has a real impact in creating software which provide innovative solutions.

Others describe me as a **flexible** person - easy to adapt to new situations.

I am hard working with a positive attitude and willingness to learn and to gain experience. I find myself as a quick knowledge taker and creative person with a hint of empathy. I am open to offer my support according to my experience in fields of design, business, production and customer service, which may be helpful when creating user friendly software.

Education

10/2019 – 18/09/2020 - Software Development Academy, Java from scratch (400 h – every weekend, excl. statutory holidays)

Programming course, focused around:

Java programming language & technologies involved:

Java, TDD, Maven, GIT, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, JDBC, Hibernate, JSP, Servlets, spring, Scrum.

Resulting repository of **projects**

Link: https://github.com/matned666?tab=repositories

My final project: https://mrndesign.eu/

2006 - 2008 - College of Arts and Design, Łódź, Poland

Commercial photography, Advertisement, Modern media (not finished, 1,5 y./ 2y., due to work in the Netherlands).

2002 - 2005 - AFA, Wroclaw, Poland Artistic photography college

Modern media – digital photography, reportage,

Photoshop, Drawing, Painting

Resulting a group exhibition of diploma works

Link: http://artpicture.home.pl

1998 – 2002 - High school no. XX in Wroclaw, profiled – computer science

Resulting a basics knowledge of C++, Turbo Pascal

Additional Courses

Cyber security with HackerU – online course focusing on offensive security –
 Red Team – basics of web protocols, system virtualisation, basics of network hardware and software, bash script, Kali Linux

- Android from scratch, online programming apps course (20 h)

Resulting an some own projects

Link: https://github.com/matniedbal/First android app

Other 100% own android project:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=pl.design.mrn.matned.dogmanagementapp

 Other online courses: Spring, MySQL, SQLite, Hibernate, Microsoft Azure, Docker

Experience

02/2012 – 03/2021 Manufacture MRN http://manufacture-mrn.pl/ Member of the board

- Designing and crafting handmade furniture for restaurants and offices, customer service, web design, 3D visuals, technical draw, logistic.
- Work with international environment
- Web development HTML, CSS, WordPress
- Project architecture from marketing, contact with client through design to production and finish

Resulting significant interior projects

from 2007 - Own artistic projects http://artpicture.home.pl/

Graphic design, photography, individual and group exhibitions all around the world.

2010-2014 - President of World Art Games Poland - nonprofit

Creation of the Polish branch of WAG https://wagames.org

05.2008 - 01.2012 Phillips Lightning - Netherlands

Cooperation with an international team in a corporate environment.

Interests

- Programming own applications development , design
- Fencing , Ken-Jitsu, European martial arts
- Arts and Crafts Photography, graphics, blacksmithing